let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Which is the smallest city in Bulgaria?",
  answer: "Obzor",
  options: [
    "Hisarya",
    "Obzor",
    "Belogradchik",
    "Tsarevo"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "When The Battle of Achelous took place?",
  answer: "August 917",
  options: [
    "August 918",
    "September 919",
    "August 917",
    "July 917"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which alphabet ivented Saints Cyril and Methodius?",
  answer: "Glagolitic ",
  options: [
    "Latin",
    "Cyrillic",
    "Glagolitic ",
    "Arabic"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "From which people Bulgaria has derived its name?",
  answer: "Bulgars",
  options: [
    "Bulgars",
    "Goths",
    "Huns",
    "Vandals"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "From what year Bulgaria is democratic?",
  answer: "1989",
  options: [
    "1999",
    "1988",
    "1998",
    "1989"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "When was the serbo-bulgarian war?",
  answer: "1885",
  options: [
    "1885",
    "1886",
    "1888",
    "1900"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which is the oldest city in Bulgaria?",
  answer: "Plovdiv",
  options: [
    "Burgas",
    "Plovdiv",
    "Sofia",
    "Pliska"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "What is the name of the only desert in Bulgaria?",
  answer: "Pobiti Kamani",
  options: [
    "There is no desert in Bulgaria.",
    "Pobiti Kamani",
    "Kamen Bryag",
    "Zlatni Pyasaci"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "The longest river in Bulgaria is",
  answer: "Iskar",
  options: [
    "Iskar",
    "Dunav",
    "Maritsa",
    "Arda"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "In what year was the first Bulgarian state established?",
  answer: "681",
  options: [
    "688",
    "682",
    "681",
    "680"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "When was The Treaty of Berlin signed?",
  answer: "July 13, 1878",
  options: [
    "June 13, 1878",
    "July 13, 1879",
    "July 13, 1878",
    "June 13, 1879"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: "Under which King Bulgarians became Christians?",
  answer: "Boris I",
  options: [
    "Cyril",
    "Basil II",
    "Boris I",
    "Samuil"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: "The longest mountain in Bulgaria is?",
  answer: "Stara planina",
  options: [
    "Rila",
    "Stara planina",
    "Rodopi",
    "Vitosha"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: "The Mount Shulep Kamak is the place were Bulgaria limit with",
  answer: "Greece and Turkey",
  options: [
    "Macedonia and Serbia",
    "Serbia and Romania",
    "Greece and Turkey",
    "Macedonia and Greece"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: "How many kilometres of coastline does Bulgaria have?",
  answer: "354km",
  options: [
    "435km",
    "167km",
    "354km",
    "390km"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
  question: "Who was the first bulgarian president?",
  answer: "Zhelyu Zhelev",
  options: [
    "Petar Stoyanov",
    "Rumen Radev",
    "Zhelyu Zhelev",
    "Rosen Plevneliev"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
  question: "What percentage of Bulgarians live in towns or cities?",
  answer: "71%",
  options: [
    "98%",
    "82%",
    "79%",
    "71%"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
  question: "The official religion in Bulgaria is",
  answer: "Orthodox christianity",
  options: [
    "Orthodox christianity",
    "Catholic christianity",
    "Islam",
    "Judaism"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
  question: "Which is the biggest country bordering Bulgaria?",
  answer: "Turkey",
  options: [
    "Romania",
    "Greece",
    "Serbia",
    "Turkey"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
  question: "Which is the Bulgarian most famous seaside resort?",
  answer: "Sunny Beach",
  options: [
    "Kiten",
    "Tsarevo",
    "Sunny Beach",
    "Primosrsko"
  ]
},
];